AARON HARDY

Professional Financial Analyst

6 080-8289-6354

@ aaronhardy6@gmail.com

Pujimino city, Saitama, Japan

SUMMARY

Experienced financial analyst with 4+ years of experience in valuation, risk analysis, and equity research. I am seeking a financial analyst role that will enable me to utilize a blend of complex analytical skills and advanced technological acumen to increase my employer's financial efficiency.

EXPERIENCE

Assistant English Instructor

Fujimino Board of Education

2017 – present Saitama, Japan

Fujimino city is a large suburban city in Saitama, Japan

 Taught over 2,000 students communication and presentation skills in a 6-year period

Financial Analyst

Aquifer Capital

2014 – 2015 Phoenix, Arizona, USA

Aquifer is a multi-strategy hedge fund sponsor

- Advised senior-level portfolio manager utilizing financial Excel and R software models
- Reduced portfolio risk by providing detailed risk analysis on portfolio equities
- Improved investment strategy analysis by creating software-based investment algorithms

Financial Analyst

Belmont Acquisitions

Belmont is a national boutique investment bank

- Advised client entrepreneurs in business growth and management strategies with detailed firm analyses
- Increase client company public exposure by over 100% by creating company profile sheets
- Enhanced company public transparency by creating and publishing press releases

Owner and Finance Manager

Deans List Tutoring, LLC

2010 – 2015 Phoenix, Arizona, USA

Deans List Tutoring was a college tutoring service

 Improved management effectiveness by creating detailed profit and client acquisition analyses



ACCOMPLISHMENTS



Increased funding proposal output by ~300%

Researched over 20 early-stage companies as a lead analyst



Trained 50+ MBA students within a 3-year period

Taught graduate students advanced math, statistics, finance, and accounting concepts resulting in an increase in graduation rates

EDUCATION

Bachelors of Science in Finance (BS)

Arizona State University

CERTIFICATIONS

CFA Institute

CFA Exams

2018 - Passed Level III exam

CAIA Association

CAIA Exams

2014 - Passed Level II exam

STRENGTHS

Excel Modeling

Data Analysis with R

Risk Analysis

Equity Research

Fast Learner

Self-Motivated

I SPEAK

English Native



Japanese Conversational

